[wind sound]
[A heavy roar gets closer]
[intense music]
[loud flight sound]
[People sound scared]
- [Explosion sound]
- [People scream in shock]
- [Successive explosion sounds]
- [People continue to scream in surprise]
[The building rumbles]
- [Noisy air raid warning]
- [People screaming]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Sound of surprise from a passerby]
[The sound becomes distant]
[Sound becoming clearer]
"hospital"
- [Explosion sound]
- [People sound scared]
[Sound of blood flying]
[Engine acceleration sound]
[Intense music stops]
[Man's groan]
[Rough breathing sounds]
[Surrounding sounds become distant]
[Man's repeated heavy breathing]
[whooshing sound]
- [Explosion sound]
- [Female doctor in English] Everyone, calm down!
Bow your head
- [Explosion sound]
- Calm down, calm down!
- [Male doctor 1] It’s okay, it’s okay
- [Explosion sound]
- [Male Doctor 2] Calm down, calm down!
- [Child’s cry]
[The building continues to rumble]
[People sound scared]
[Distant explosion sound]
Malach!
[Welcoming sigh]
[Male doctor 1] You did it!
[Male Doctor 2] Malak!
[Female doctor] Prepare a blood transfusion, quickly!
[Male Doctor 2] Where are the antibiotics?
[Rough breathing]
[The sound of a man's heavy breathing is heard]
[Theme song]
[News Anchor 1 in Korean]
This is sad news
I was involved in a hit-and-run accident yesterday morning.
A patient being transported to the hospital
There is news that he died during transport.
The ambulance carrying Mr. A arrived last morning.
- [Siren sound]
- As many as five hospitals
had to go around
finally arrived last
In the hospital
Mr. A was diagnosed as dead.
I had no choice but to get off
[News Anchor 2] However,
Similar cases like this
There are already 13 cases this year alone.
As it is known that it occurred
‘Korea’s severe trauma system’
'It's not working properly
'Aren't you doing it?'
voices of concern
It's getting bigger
[Woman] The major trauma center is
In a general emergency room
beyond the scope of treatment
Emergency patients with fatal trauma
This is a center that provides specialized treatment.
Manpower and facilities suitable for this
To equip equipment, etc.
The Ministry of Health and Welfare will
To revitalize the severe trauma center
generous investment
We are planning
on this land
no more
So that there is no helpless death
We promise!
[Sigh] This was my ministerial inauguration speech, right?
huh?
Look at the current situation, but
[Man's light cough]
Who are you?
The best hospital in Korea
Not the directors.
But why can’t I just do this?
Why, why, why!
[The directors clear their coughs]
Director Choi Jo-eun
Yes?
Yes, Minister.
[Myunghee] Korea University Hospital
Severe trauma team
How much support did you receive?
Oh, that…
[Myunghee] You took 10 billion won.
10 billion!
So, did you get your money's worth?
[Joeun] Hey, it’s me, the severe trauma team.
I want to continue to operate well.
[Myunghee] But?
[Jo Eun] But now in our country
He's a major trauma specialist.
Someone who can do it
There's only one person.
yes
-You collapsed from overwork.
- [Joeun] Yes
Until now, Professor Kwon
You have led the severe trauma team well.
How can I do this anymore?
You can't do it, can you?
Professor Kwon Hak-soo collapses
Everyone saw it with their own eyes
Pushing it into place
Would you like to sit down?
There is
Who?
[Humorous sound effects]
- [Heavy sound effect]
- [Siren sound]
[Interesting music]
[Myunghee] I
far away
We have brought you a great person.
You will arrive soon
[In-house broadcasting sound]
[Guide voice] Professor Ahn Jeong-won of the Department of Pediatrics
Please come to operating room number 12.
We inform you once again
- [Guide voice continues to play]
- [Busy sound]
[Interesting music fades out]
[News Anchor] Severe trauma specialist
known as a pioneer
Professor Hak-Soo Kwon of Hankuk University Hospital
The news is that he collapsed from overwork.
- [long sigh]
- The barren severe trauma system
Professor Kwon was called a lonely hero.
- At Korea University Hospital…
- Well said, a lonely hero.
[News Anchor] After taking the first step
For the development of our country’s emergency medical system
I threw my whole body into it
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
- Professor Kwon has been
The reason why I suffered from excessive work
A stable working environment...
[Man] Yes, this is Jaewon Yang, a general surgeon.
[Woman] Teacher, go to the ambulance now.
We are transporting a patient with severe trauma.
On the left upper abdomen, the staff wound
They say I'm unconscious
- [Man humming sound]
- [Staff] Patient 37
I'll take you this way.
- Patient 37
- [Call ring sound]
[Jaewon] My blood pressure is completely
You don't get caught?
What about the C line?
- I'll go as quickly as possible.
- [Sound of footsteps moving away]
[Interesting music]
[Sound of rustling envelope]
- [Jaewon’s urgent breathing]
- [Card recognition sound]
[Sound of rolling carrier wheels]
[In-house broadcasting sound]
[Guide voice] Neurosurgery
Professor Seung-Hyeon Noh...
- [Guide voice continues to play]
- [Busy sound]
[Continuously noisy]
- [Siren sound]
- [Uneasy music]
[Paramedic] This is Shinhwan.
Staff wound, left abdomen.
- [Doctor 1] Uh, to the resuscitation room!
- [Doctor 2] Yes!
BP drops, 60!
[Jaewon] I’ll intubate right away.
- Be careful not to touch the knife.
- [Doctor 2] Yes!
[Doctor 1] One, two, three!
[Sound of strength]
[Doctor 1] Unconscious
Heart rate is also at a dangerous level
[Jaewon] But this is a knife
It's stuck so there's not much bleeding.
- [Doctor 1] Check BP
- [Doctor 2] Yes
[Jaewon] Oh, cut that carefully.
If a sword is pulled out, it will be a big problem.
- Yes
- [Doctor 1] Intubation is complete.
- [Beeping warning sound]
- [Doctor 2] BP drops further, 50!
[Jaewon] What, 50?
Oh, come on, let's hurry.
Get ready for CT, quickly.
- [Doctor 1] Yes, yes
- [Doctor 2] Yes
Now, now, now, now, wait a minute, wait a minute
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
What is this?
[dark music]
[Doctor 2] Is there a bruise?
- Give me the stethoscope.
- [Nurse 1] Yes
[Jaewon] Blood accumulates in the pericardium
putting pressure on the heart
[Heavy heartbeat sound]
Cardiac Tampons
Please call the thoracic surgery department.
When the thoracic surgeon comes, they will puncture you.
Spinal needle and ultrasound
Please prepare it right away.
- [Doctor 2] Yes
- Yes
[Jaewon] Ultrasound
quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly
[Jaewon's urgent breathing]
- [Sound of running footsteps]
- [Nurse 2] Teacher!
All thoracic surgeons are undergoing surgery.
They say it takes 2 hours.
Did I mention Cardiac tampons?
That's called a heart rupture...
Man, I'm going crazy, really.
[Jaewon] What should I do?
Should I do the puncture?
heart problem
Maybe not.
By taking a CT scan
Shouldn't you check first?
- Hey, what, CT?
- [Beeping warning sound]
[Doctor 2] Oh!
BP critical level, 40!
- [Nervous music]
- [Doctor 1] Teacher
Shouldn’t we start with the 1000 characters?
teacher!
Oh, I'll do it, yeah!
Please
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Yes
- [Jaewon] I do it.
[panting] Come on, come on
I'm going
[Jaewon’s nervous breathing]
[Sound of wind blowing]
- [Music that heightens tension]
- [Repeated nervous breathing]
[The sound becomes distant]
[The tense music fades]
- [Sound becomes clearer]
- [Each person screams in surprise]
Who are you?
[Jaewon’s surprised voice]
[Calm music]
[Man] Gypoid Process
45 degrees to the left
[Muttering] No, no, no...
uh?
[Fast beeping sound from medical equipment]
[Consistent beep sound]
Huh?
- [The beeping sound becomes slower]
- Huh?
- [Doctor 2] Oh, BP is back.
- [Constant ECG beep sound]
- [Sound of taking off gloves]
- [Jaewon] Huh?
[Elasticity of financial resources]
Who are you?
Hey, you're an emergency medicine guy.
Can’t you even spell a thousand letters properly?
Me?
I'm an anal major.
[clattering sound]
But why are you going to the emergency room?
Because I’m on duty.
We are general surgery
Thoracic Surgery, Neurosurgery
- [Pisik]
- I go around like this and look on duty.
It's absurd.
[rustling sound]
[Jaewon laughs]
[Jaewon] No, whatever.
- Are you a doctor?
- [Sound of putting on gloves]
Well, whatever it is
Thank you for your help.
Could you please leave now?
This is my area.
- [Sound of repeatedly putting on gloves]
- It's not over yet.
[Jaewon] No, who are you?
[Man] Starting today, I am a professor at this hospital.
- Severe trauma surgery
- [Sound of gloves thumping]
[Jaewon laughs] What, that’s ridiculous.
[Sound of gloves being put on repeatedly]
Uh, that…
- [Meaningful music]
- Professor Kwon’s successor
Minutes, minutes?
This is not your area
It's my area
This is Baek Kang-hyuk.
Hey, anus
Now what are you going to do next?
ah…
- It's not anus, it's Jaewon Yang.
- [Kanghyuk is tired]
[Kang Hyuk] I only call useful people by name.
Now what are you going to do next?
What's next?
Uh, I grabbed a Cardiac tampon.
I need to check for stab wounds. CT?
[Kanghyuk snorts] CT?
this patient
Around at the time of rescue
There was a broken blade
Hey, anus
When treating patients with severe trauma
The patient's current condition is also important, but
Understanding the circumstances at the time of the accident
You know what's important, don't you?
[Jaewon] Yes? Oh, I know.
[Kang Hyuk] But the patient
Where and how were you stabbed?
Did you check?
[Jaewon] No
[Detective 1] Gangster?
-What about the weapon?
- [Detective 2] It’s called a raw fish knife.
I was stabbed severely in the upper abdomen...
[Detectives' surprised sounds]
[Kang Hyuk] So the stab wound itself is
I thought it was no big deal
First, I pulled out the knife.
So how was it?
[Jaewon] Even if I pull out the knife, it bleeds
It wasn't as much as I thought
[Kanghyuk] That’s right, from the beginning
Because I was stabbed with a broken knife.
The wound would have been shallow
Then what is it?
- My blood pressure is shit.
- [Bright music]
Consciousness is unclear
It's because of Cardiac tampons.
Now what's the next step?
What's the next step?
hmm…
- Gauze, a lot.
- [Nurse 1] Yes
[Jaewon hesitates] Gauze
Gauze, why gauze?
The patient is still conscious
That you didn't come back
There is a cause here too.
Get ready, it's going to explode
Exploding, exploding, exploding?
[nervous music]
- Uh, uh, what, what!
- [Beeping warning sound]
[Kanghyuk] Call the anesthesiology department
Everyone prepare for surgery
[Together] Yes!
[busy sound]
[Sound of taking off gloves]
[Man] Hand of God?
Even people who are out of breath
Just with one scalpel
[Chuckling] Are you going to save me or something?
[Doctor 1] No, such a skilled person
There's no way I don't know
Aren’t you from Korea University?
What, are you from overseas?
[Doctor 2] Muhan Daerae
[Doctor 1] Huh? infinity?
Wuhan University?
[Doctor 2] Still, in its own way
I drank some foreign water
Where?
international peace conference
Ha!
what else can i say
It's not just a volunteer organization.
Are there one or two doctors from there?
Ah, ace, ace
- [Grumbling] What is Ace...
- Is this the Syrian team? 6 years there
The trauma called trauma is
You must have heard about it all?
It's all about hard work, right?
No, but I'm from Infinite
How did you come to Korea University Hospital, huh?
How did you get here?
Is there anything else but parachutes?
just up there
It was put straight down.
Who are you, huh?
Is that Baek Kang-hyuk or something?
A man who is placed vertically
Kang Myung-hee
Kang Myung-hee?
- [Sound of grabbing]
- Now, wait a minute.
Kang Myung-hee?
Is that Kang Myung-hee that I know?
[Interesting music]
[Sound of approaching car]
[Doctor 1] So
At the appointment ceremony of a professor
The Minister of Health and Welfare
Would you like to attend?
[Doctor 2] Oh, I don’t know.
Is it Kang Myeong-hee or Kangnaengi?
It's so annoying, really, kid.
[Doctor 1] No, just one parachute.
[Chuckling] What are you going to do?
Oh my, it’s nonsense, it’s nonsense, hehe!
[vibration sound]
[Sunwoo’s heavy breathing]
- Uh, why?
- [Male] Teacher Hwang Seon-woo
This is the emergency room.
The major trauma team today
Since you’re on anesthesia duty…
Ah, hey, that's over there, not me.
Do it at another hospital.
[Man] Oh, that’s not right
The patient's condition is a bit serious...
Hey, so look at me now
Come in?
Oh, no, that's not it.
[Sunwoo] Hey, I’m off in the afternoon.
- I'll be home from work soon.
- [Kang Hyuk] What, dating?
[Sunwoo] Hey, and you
If you think surgery will work,
Please call me in advance
Gotta make sure I get ready
Oh, he's real
A 4-year resident like this
Do you have no sense at all? uh?
When are you going to become a person? uh?
When will you become a human?
Oh my gosh, Mr. [Tsk mouth sound]
- Speak softly...
- what?
Hello, what did you just say?
Who are you?
- [Kang Hyuk] He’s a professor, you bastard.
- [Interesting Music]
- School, professor?
- [Kang Hyuk] Mr. Lee
What are you doing, bastard?
Know when a patient will appear
‘Make contact in advance, Mara!’
No, that's not it, ah, I
I was on duty yesterday as well.
Don't criticize me
Won't you come out right away?
When I went to the operating room
If it's not there, I feel lost, really.
Don't answer!
Yes, yes, I understand.
- What!
- [Sound of putting down]
Hey, professor!
Well, but
Full of regular surgeries
There are no empty operating rooms in the main building right now...
- [Interesting music fades out]
- Mr...
Fortunately, there is an emergency operating room.
Let's go
[Heavy music]
[Constant ECG beeping sound]
[Jaewon’s awkward voice]
[Financial resources] With subsidies
I did some remodeling...
For cotton use
I made one in a hurry.
Is everything going well?
[Jaewon] But almost
never used
[Kang Hyuk] Who is the head of the severe trauma team now?
[Sound of cabinet door rattling]
[Jaewon] None.
[Kanghyuk’s tsk mouth sound]
[Sighing] The house looks like this
It's going well, wow
- [Jaewon] Well, it’s still okay
- Uh, ‘Thank you.’
[Jaewon] In the meantime, I was working in the emergency medicine department.
Thank you for your support...
What is this
It's not even a local corner store, Mr.
[Heavy breathing]
I'm here!
- Anesthesiology?
- [Sunwoo gasps] Yes
Ah, earlier…
The person who called...
- [Sunwoo’s repeated heavy breathing]
- [Heavy music stops]
Hey, chestnuts
Let’s save the patient first.
yes
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
[Interesting music]
[Shoot water sound]
- [button clicking sound]
- [The sound of water stops]
[Heavy music]
[Constant ECG beeping sound]
[Kanghyuk’s long breathing sound]
[Kang Hyuk] Scalpel
[clattering sound]
[Inhaler operating sound]
[Kanghyuk] Hey, anus
It's pretty quick
[Jaewon] Oh, well, this much…
But my name is
Not anal, but Yangjae…
[Kanghyuk] Yes, it’s here
One of the splenic artery trunks was severed.
So the blood pours
[Jaewon] Oh!
[Kang Hyuk] ‘Oh’?
- [Jaewon’s awkward voice]
-Why don’t you tie it quickly?
[Jaewon] Ah, yes, yes, right away
I'll tie it, but...
- [Heavy music fades away]
-Where should I tie it?
[Kanghyuk’s sigh]
[Kang Hyuk] Can’t you see this?
[Tsk mouth sound] Right angle
- [Heavy music]
- [rattling sound]
Yes, to the average person
You won't see it
[Jaewon] Oh!
- oh!
- [Kang Hyuk] Don’t you wear a tie?
[Jaewon] Yes!
Black Silk Three-Oh, please give me one
[Sound of being handed something]
[Kanghyuk] Wait a minute
[dark music]
[Jaewon] Professor, I think the blood was a waste.
It seeps out more.
[Kang Hyuk] This guy is really...
[Tsk mouth sound]
[Jaewon] Did I make a mistake?
- [Kang Hyuk] Hey!
- [Jaewon’s surprised voice]
- [Dark music stops]
- [Speed up electrocardiogram beeping sound]
[Sunwoo] Yes?
[Kang Hyuk] Did you use vasopressors?
[Sunwoo] Yes, the blood, blood pressure
It's only 40 out of 60...
[Kanghyuk looks angry] That’s right
Do you use vasopressors?
With Cardiac Tampons
A patient who even underwent puncture?
[Sunwoo] No, I am
My blood pressure is only 40 out of 60...
[Kang Hyuk] You tried to blow your nose without using your hands.
Does that look like you're screwed?
Hey, resident.
You should call me right away
Bring in another anesthesia
[Sunwoo] School, professor
Anyway, this
I think you went a little too far.
[Kang Hyuk] It’s too much!
I'll be comfortable
Is the bastard who screwed up the patient a doctor?
A guy who isn't even a doctor
Can I stay in the operating room?
[loudly] Huh?
[Kanghyuk’s tsk mouth sound]
Now, the rest
Because I need to check my heart
Finish suturing and prepare thoracotomy.
- [Jaewon] Yes
- [Doctor] Yes
[Interesting music]
- Ha, Mr...
- [clattering sound]
- Kick out the anesthesiologist?
- [Doctor] You're crazy.
Honestly, the best of all surgeries is
Isn’t this our department?
But, even in the surgical field,
Professor of trauma surgery
Should I give it to the anesthesiologist?
Hey, hey, so
Who wants to go?
You know, that bastard.
Sigh!
- [Interesting music stops]
- [Man] … five, six, seven
On the other side
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
- Two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
[Continuously noisy]
Yes, anesthesiology and pain medicine
This is resident Park Gyeong-won.
[Doctor] Wow, it’s an emergency.
- Jump to the emergency operating room.
- [Interesting Music]
[sigh]
I'm studying
Do I really have to go?
[Doctor] Hey, it sucks
Are you a fellow?
It's an emergency surgery!
Where are you being cocky? [Tsk mouth sound]
- [Sigh]
- [Putting down sound]
[Sound of dumbbells rattling]
- [Interesting music stops]
- [ECG meter beep sound]
[Interesting music]
[Inhaler operating sound]
[Continued inhaler operating sound]
[Kang Hyuk] But…
[Jaewon] Yes?
[Kanghyuk] Not you, anesthesiologist
[Kyungwon] Yes
[Kang Hyuk] This is heart rate
Did you shorten it on purpose?
There is less movement
[Inhaler operating sound]
[Kyungwon] I thought it could be Rupture.
[Kang Hyuk] What is it? What's your name?
[Kyungwon] This is Park Kyungwon.
[Kanghyuk] Rupture is right
[clattering sound]
- Come on, let's speed up.
- [Inhaler operating sound]
Three-five please
[Sound of clattering down]
[Call connection tone]
- [Interesting music stops]
- [Noisy sound]
[Voice guidance] Can't connect
- [Bitter mouth noise]
- After the beep...
[Muttering] Where on earth?
What are you doing?
I'm not even answering the phone
[Man] The Minister is coming!
[Sound of door opening]
[Myunghee] Hello
yes, hello
hello
[Jo Eun and Myunghee’s laughter]
[Jo Eun] Oh, Minister, this is it
You're busy, but you can't go this far
- It's an honor.
- [Myunghee] Hey, what are you saying?
Our Professor Baek Kang-hyuk
What will you do in the future?
I'm very excited
Oh, actually, Professor Baek is still…
Ah, yes
Well, let's wait, yeah
Where do you sit here...
- Ah, this way, this way.
- [Myunghee] Yes, yes
Yes, hi… Please sit down [laughter]
[Joeun] Yes, please sit down. Please sit down.
[Joeun’s exhaling sound]
[Joeun’s awkward laughter]
- [Interesting Music]
- [Tickling sound effect]
[Constant ECG beeping sound]
[mumbling sound]
[Doctor 1] What time is it?
Are you still not coming?
[Doctor 2] I have no concept of time
Ah, indeed
[Kang Hyuk] Now, cut.
Now, let's close our hearts.
end
[Interesting music fades out]
[Operation room door sound]
[Jaewon] 1 hour 42 minutes
- [rattling button sound]
- [Bitter mouth noise]
[long breathing sound]
Like this
It's not a surgery that ends quickly.
Oh my, what a surprise!
[Kang Hyuk] Fast, Mr.
You'll be done in an hour and a half, huh?
You went over it by more than 10 minutes.
Because someone is providing assistance like a bullshit.
What a piece of cake.
[Kanghyuk] I was late because of you
Huh? My Professor Appointment Ceremony
Have you started already?
yes?
[Screaming] It’s already too late
I have to go and see if the patient wakes up.
You're not going?
- No, it's still my appointment ceremony...
- [Bitter mouth noise]
I need to see the patient wake up.
[Jaewon] Oh, no, professor.
Hurry, go quickly
[Hmm exhaling sound]
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
Oh, it's special
- [Roaring sound]
- [Myunghee] Well, let’s wait a moment.
[Joeun] Yes [sound of taking in breath]
[Doctor 1] Minister Kang calls Baek Kang-hyuk
I understand why it was recommended.
It's probably for preparation for the National Assembly inspection.
The fact that the director gave the OK is also [Pisik]
Well, just from infinity
I left it in a shabby mess
Severe trauma team
I want to create a famous studio.
[Doctor 1’s bitter mouth]
What I don't know is, bro.
Why did you come to our hospital? huh?
Even though I knew for sure that I would be ostracized
[Doctor 2’s snoring sound]
[Moon So-ri]
[Roaring sound]
- [Doctor 3] What time is it, by the way?
- [Doctor 4] Is there anyone who is not busy?
[Joeun] I’m here, I’m here
I'm here, yeah
[Continued whispering]
[Doctor 5] Ugh, cheesy, me.
- [Doctor 6] There is no concept of time.
- [Continued whispering]
[Jo Eun] Professor Baek, you’re late.
[Kanghyuk] Yes, it’s late
[Whispering] I, that, apple first
Do it first
I think it would be a good idea to start
Oh, here, here
Let’s start by saying hello to the Minister.
- [Myunghee] I'm fine
- [Joeun] Huh? yes, yes
[Kang Hyuk] You’re okay.
[Sound of bitter mouth]
hello
Appointed as professor of trauma surgery
This is Baek Kang-hyuk.
Well, the director here
They say I should start by apologizing.
I can't do that.
[mumbling sound]
Shouldn’t I receive the apology?
I'd like to
- [Rumbling sound]
- [Interesting Music]
Well, they even gave me a professor position.
Reorganization of the severe trauma team
I came because they said they would order it for me.
What is this…
Well, roughly speaking, I'm the boss of pants.
I think I found it
[Kang Hyuk’s laughter and tsk noise]
Ah, well, anyway I
Why did you come to Korea University Hospital?
- [Continued whispering]
- [Doctor 7] What…
Severe trauma team
- [Sound of hitting]
- [Interesting music fades out]
[Emphasis sound effect]
I’m here to take down the shutter!
[Whispers]
[Whispering] No, Professor Baek.
Why is this happening?
Professor Baek, come with me for a moment.
Let's talk
- uh? Let’s talk first…
- [Doctor 1] Wait a minute!
Ah, yes!
Ah, Professor Baek Kang-hyuk.
Yes [mouthing sound]
Professor of trauma surgery
That's not what you want to say.
It was also the first day of my appointment.
'Even if reality is not easy
I'll do my best!'
Well, like this
Shouldn’t we do it?
[mumbling sound]
Ah!
For your information, I am the Chief of Surgery.
Professor of Anal Surgery
My name is Han Yu-rim.
Yes, Professor Hang Yu-rim.
No, not Hang Yu-rim, Han Yu-rim
This is Mr. Han
Yes, thank you for your words.
Oh, I actually did it before the appointment ceremony.
What are the skills of a high-level hospital?
I looked at the liver
It was very embarrassing.
[Kang Hyuk’s yawning mouth sound]
After listening to the story
Until now, trauma surgery
It's not separate
- In other surgeries
- [Interesting Music]
On duty at the severe trauma team
They took turns standing there
- [Tapping sound]
- Like spinning a bomb
- [Jo Eun] Professor Baek, me, word choice…
- I don't know anything about trauma.
Anal surgeon on duty alone
I'm struggling
- [Roaring sound]
- What?
So carefully
So sincerely
The sight of trying to kill someone
never seen it
- [Roaring sound]
- Let's see this.
Is this really...
[Kang Hyuk] This system
The system is a mess
The doctor on duty is a quack
I have no choice but to do it
[Doctor 8] Let’s listen, let’s listen.
There's nothing I can't say
[Yurim] Hey, Professor Baek!
Be careful what you say!
[Doctor 9] Talks too much
Isn't that harsh?
[Yurim] What kind of quack are you talking about?
I'm doing this
[Doctor 10] What a quack!
[Yurim] Who is looking at whom?
They say he’s a quack!
That quack is killing people
Because I can't just watch
I had to do the surgery quickly and come back.
It's late
So I can't apologize
So!
I'm going to take down the shutter!
[Doctor 11] No, what are you talking about?
[Yurim] Hey, do you think we’re funny?
- uh? Is Korea University Hospital funny?
- [Doctor 12] Are you that handsome?
[Doctors’ angry shouting]
Now, Mr. Minister, you must not misunderstand.
[Joeun's embarrassed voice]
[Whispering] Professor Baek!
However, the severe trauma team
Take down the sign
Upgrade to one level
Severe trauma…
We will be reborn as a center
[Interesting music stops]
[Quiet]
[Jo Eun] Three, three, three, center?
[Doctor 13] It doesn’t sound like words.
Doing it!
[Yurim] Are you doing whatever you want?
This, now, huh?
- [Interesting Music]
- [Doctors’ angry shouting]
Minister, will you push it?
Yes, we will watch.
As much as 10 billion won invested
I'll let you pick the mulberry.
In the future I
I'll show you right
Here are my thoughts
That's it, the end
- [Yurim] No, what are you!
- [Jo Eun] Professor Baek, Professor Baek
[Yurim] Huh? Where are you going, aren't you coming?
hey!
[Doctor 14] I have to apologize, apologize!
[Joeun] Hey, hey
Oh my, Professor Baek.
Professor Baek!
[Yurim] Hey!
A university with no genealogy anywhere.
I dare to add that
Our Professor Baek Kang-hyuk’s expression is
Although it seems a bit rough
Well, I don't think it's wrong.
I guarantee your skills
Trust me and give me a chance
thank you
[Joeun] Oh, oh, me, Minister
Jang…
[Yurim] Applause
[Emphasis sound effect]
What, what, what? nickname?
- [Woman 1] What is it?
- [Woman 2 laughing] What is it?
[mumbling sound]
[Woman 1] Let’s go quickly, just
[Woman 2] Let’s go, let’s go
Earlier, the professor said ‘anus’…
Hey, hey, is that a nickname?
You're just teasing me
[Kyungwon] Still, the professor is a senior.
It seemed like you liked it.
Teach like a disciple
Disciple? Hey, hey
You're talking about big trouble, man.
The best in general surgery
Leave the anal surgery alone
some crazy guy
Trauma surgery without vision
Apply for a detailed department, huh?
Just look at our hospital right now, just
Just the name, just the pattern
It's a major trauma team.
[Kyungwon] That’s right
Professor Haksu Kwon also worked hard alone...
I can never do that, I won't
Anal surgery is just a name.
How great is the view?
There are almost no emergencies and it is easy to open a clinic.
The income is also good
[Kyungwon] I see.
You are truly perfect for anal surgery.
That's a good nickname
I enjoyed my coffee
- [Laughter of people far away]
- [Sound of footsteps moving away]
That's true, but it's strangely annoying.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, this is Jaewon Yang of general surgery.
Hey, where are you?
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Sound of returning footsteps]
[Jaewon] Huh?
uh?
Where have you been?
[bell sound]
yes
I came to see that patient.
[Screaming loudly] Who are you?
[Kang Hyuk] Professor of trauma surgery
This is Baek Kang-hyuk.
to our hospital
There is no such professor.
Carelessly pretending to be a professor
You can't do that.
- [Humorous sound effects]
- Oh, hey.
- I'm a real professor here.
- [Interesting Music]
in it in the morning
I had thoracotomy surgery.
No, don't speak informally.
No, I came to see the patient.
That's because it's blocked!
Don't raise your voice too much
Because there are patients inside
-Patient… [sigh]
- [Nurse] Patient’s name
How are you?
[Muttering] No, I
I didn't see the patient's name, but...
uh!
brought the patient
I know the doctor's name
His name is…
He…
anus?
[Interesting music crackles to a halt]
- [click click]
- That sounds like an asshole.
Oh, hey, hey!
hey!
Mr. I
This is cheeky, Mr. [Tsk mouth sound]
- [Sound of running footsteps]
- [Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
Hey, anus!
you came at the right time
[in a loud voice] Professor Baek...
- [Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
- ‘Professor Baek’ is informal, and this…
no…
I was looking for Professor Baek.
Me?
why?
Bukhansan Mountain
On the Bukhansan Mountain hiking trail
It's a trip accident.
- [Heavy music]
- There is an emergency patient.
[Sound of strong wind]
But
The injury was so severe that transport was required.
I don't know if I can live
-What about the transport helicopter? Did you get there?
- [Jaewon] That…
At the Central Rescue Team
It starts this way.
[Kang Hyuk] Then what, transfer helicopter?
Come here first
We can go and treat it ourselves.
yes
Us?
- [Music stops]
-Why, what's the problem?
What are we?
me and you
Well, for now
[Card recognition sound]
Call me when the transport helicopter is ready, okay?
Because I'll be watching the patient
Be sure to pack an emergency kit!
Now, wait a minute! me, me, me
[Meaningful sound effects]
Taking a helicopter?
[Humorous sound effects]
Me too?
Uh, emergency intensive care unit.
[Sighing] Internal medicine?
emergency intensive care unit
The intensive care unit in the main building is a mess.
[Beep button sound]
[Kanghyuk’s elasticity]
- [Interesting Music]
- [Beep button sound]
Who are you? How did you get in?
Your voice looks familiar
Huh?
That stubbornness from earlier?
What are you talking about?
Wow, don't say anything weird.
Get out quickly
This is a place where only medical staff come in.
No, I'm the medic.
Okay, that's it.
What's your name?
[Nurse] What if I know your name?
[clattering sound]
[Kang Hyuk] ‘A thousand roses’
Okay? Ah, now
- Wow, get out.
- Ouch!
- [Beep button sound]
- Get out, get out.
- [Kanghyuk] Oh! Ouch, ouch!
- Oh, let's go, let's go
- [Kang Hyuk] Ah!
- No, not that one.
- This way, this way, this way
- [Kang Hyuk] No, wait, that’s me.
- Oh, what is it?
- [Kang Hyuk] Oh, wait a minute, Mr.!
uh?
- [Meaningful sound effects]
- Tattoo?
- uh?
- [Emphasis sound effect]
Over there too?
[Sound of intake of breath]
[Kanghyuk] No, that patient
The patient I treated
‘Treatment’?
[Cool music]
[Music increases and then stops]
- [Constant ECG beep sound]
- [Sound of approaching footsteps]
[clattering sound]
[dark music]
- [Kanghyuk’s moans]
- [Patient’s sound of strength]
[Glass shards clatter]
[Kanghyuk’s heavy breathing]
- [Patient moans]
- [Continued heavy breathing]
[Sound of being shot]
[Whooshing sound of gas leaking]
[Heavy breathing]
[Sound of exhaling]
[nervous music]
[Rose] Oh, no, no!
[urgent breathing]
[The tense music fades]
[troublesome sound]
Oh… No, no, no.
- [Sound of strength]
- Oh, what...
- Wow
- Let go of this, let go of this.
- Why is it so strong?
- [The sound of roses giving strength]
- Hey, why are you so strong?
- Oh, this guy is real!
[Kang Hyuk] Oh, hey! This woman…
[Rose] Oh, oh!
[Kang Hyuk] Just be quiet, Mr...
- Oh, stop...
- [Jaewon] Oh!
- I didn't see anything.
- [Rose] Oh, Teacher Jaewon, report it!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Don't misunderstand!
- [Rose] Report it to the police!
[Kanghyuk] Don’t misunderstand
It's not like that
- [Rose] Report, report to the police!
- [Jaewon] Police, police…
- [Kanghyuk] Oh, this woman
- Police, uh-uh, please calm down.
- Don't come!
- [Rose’s heavy breathing]
[Rose] Teacher Jaewon!
This guy is a gangster!
[mumbling sound]
[sigh]
It's not
- [Puzzling sound]
- He's a professor.
[Kang Hyuk] Mr. Ai!
[Jaewon] No, you are the professor.
This is Professor Baek Kang-hyuk.
- [Humorous music]
- [surprised gasp]
[Kanghyuk’s sigh]
[Rose] Oh my
sorry
[Kang Hyuk] Gangster?
When I see
That one looks more like a gangster.
No, the professor earlier
You treated the patient...
[sigh]
sorry
That, Nurse Cheon Mi-mi?
From today onwards...
He's a gangster
gangster
Yes?
[click button sound]
- [Sharp sound effect]
- [The humorous music fades out]
[Patient] Only when you die do you get tissue
I thought I was escaping
[Patient's heavy breathing]
Thanks to the teacher...
Please save someone like me too.
No matter who the patient is
whatever you did
doesn't matter
I'm just a doctor
I just did my job
Actually…
The most important thing is
The patient met me.
I saved it because it was me.
Do you understand what I mean?
[Humorous sound effects]
Oh well, if you meet a quack
By now at the Jordan River
Well, are you having a picnic?
Doing some tanning
- [Kanghyuk’s laughter]
- [Clears cough]
Ah!
A child and this teacher
This teacher saved the patient's life.
You just did a great job.
The stomach side that teacher Lee sewed was
It'll probably be barely noticeable.
It's really the hand of God
[laughter]
[Jaewon] Me, me, me, me?
- [Patient] Thank you so much.
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
Uh, huh?
Yes, this is Jaewon Yang of general surgery.
Now? yes, i understand
Well, the helicopter arrived.
Wow, take care of yourselves
[Jaewon] Yes
- [Button click sound]
- [Jaewon] Oh, teacher Jang Mi.
[Kang Hyuk] Hey, gangster
Check that patient's vitals every 30 minutes.
Uh, yes, I understand.
- [Kanghyuk] Jump, anus!
- [Jaewon] Yes!
[Sound of running footsteps]
Anus?
Are you a gangster?
- [Interesting Music]
- Ah...
It's a nickname, a nickname
[upbeat music]
Uh oh, oh!
Just a moment, Professor!
- why!
- [Jaewon] It’s not there.
It's over there at the heliport.
Isn't it a rooftop?
Yes, it's out there.
Hey, let's talk about it sooner, Mr.
[helicopter sound]
[Jaewon] Uh, uh!
- Uh, uh
- [Helicopter sound gets closer]
Ah, ah!
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
No, is this a heliport?
Yes, that's true.
Professor, please come back.
- Hey, move forward.
- Yes?
- [Jaewon’s embarrassed voice]
- If you do it wrong, it gets caught in the propeller.
Forward, forward?
- I have to get on the helicopter now. I have to get on the helicopter now.
- No, no, really no.
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
Ugh, really, really, ah, ugh!
[Jaewon continues to sound scared]
Let's go!
[Jaewon] Please save me…
Wow, wow, it's real!
Oh, please save me!
[Jaewon's scared scream]
Ouch! Please save me!
Ouch!
[loud helicopter sound]
[Helicopter sound continues]
[The cheerful music fades away]
[Man] From above
The official notice came down a year ago.
With the teachers
It's my first time riding with you.
[Kang Hyuk] Now, just like eating
You will be dispatched
What's your name?
This is Ahn Joong-heon, team leader of the Central Rescue Team.
But have you ever flown in a helicopter?
Well, how can you not tremble?
Oh, well, this is normal.
It's usually like that
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
[Kanghyuk] Hey, anus, that’s why you are like this
Can you save the patient?
I have a fear of heights.
There's a long way to go, a long way to go
[Jaewon’s groaning]
[Beeping warning sound]
[click button operation sound]
[Beeping electronic sound]
[Captain] The weather is cloudy
My vision is serious
- A gust of wind blows
- [Heavy music]
[First Officer] Captain, no more
Access seems to be difficult
[Jungheon sighs]
- [Radio radio operating sound]
-What is the situation on site?
- [Rescue worker] Current patient situation
It's serious
- [Sound of strong wind]
- In unconsciousness
My pulse is very faint.
on the right side of the chest at the time of the fall.
Was there a shock?
Also on the ribs
Looks damaged
[Jungheon] How much longer can I hold out?
[Rescue worker] Right now
need to be treated
You are coming with a doctor, right?
It is difficult to transport in its current state.
If you do not receive immediate medical attention
miss the patient
You'll have to hurry, captain.
It's impossible
I can't go any further because of the gusts of wind.
Yes?
[Captain] If this continues, we will all die.
You have to turn back
[Kanghyuk’s sigh]
- Well, there's nothing I can do.
- [Jaewon] Huh?
uh?
- [Kanghyuk] Hold on tight
- [Jungheon] Ah, sir, professor.
- [Kanghyuk’s heavy breathing]
[Captain] Hey, what a surprise, Mr.
Can't you?
[Captain] What is it?
Take a seat, quickly.
Wow, I think I can go.
- [Captain] Team Leader Ahn, what are you doing?
- [Uneasy music]
[Sound of strong wind]
[Rescuer] Just between us
Can't I take you down?
You know it's impossible
[sound of helicopter in the distance]
Oh! [Rough breathing]
- [Clicking sound]
- [Crackling sound]
[Helicopter sounds continuing in the distance]
[intense music]
[Captain’s surprised voice]
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
Captain
Let’s touch the baton.
[Captain] Yes…
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
We're here, pack your bags and get ready quickly.
Are they all there? Are they all there?
[clattering sound of equipment]
[Jaewon's repeated heavy breathing]
[Jaewon's scared scream]
Close it, close it, close it
Close it, quickly.
[Jaewon continues to sound scared]
Come quickly!
I can't, I really can't.
You were on that helicopter.
Really, really, really, really
I really can't, I can't.
[Kanghyuk] Hey, anus
- Would it be like this even if it were your family?
- [Jaewon] No, no, no.
[groaning sound]
[Continuous groaning]
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
[Jaewon's repeated sounds of surprise]
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
no! [Sounds scared again and again]
Professor, now
You're not going to jump, are you?
- [Jaewon’s Scream]
- I go first.
[Jaewon] Please save me!
-No one!
- [Jungheon] Professor!
[screaming]
[The sound echoes distantly]
[upbeat music]